export const php = [
    {
        question: "What does PHP stand for?",
        option1: "Personal Home Page",
        option2: "Hypertext Preprocessor",
        option3: "Public Hosting Platform",
        option4: "Personal Hosting Platform",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is the correct way to start a PHP script?",
        option1: "<?php",
        option2: "<script>",
        option3: "<?",
        option4: "<?=",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is used to comment out a single line in PHP?",
        option1: "/ This is a  comment",
        option2: "/* This is a comment */",
        option3: "# This is a comment",
        option4: "// This is a comment",
        ans: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "What function is used to output data to the browser in PHP?",
        option1: "echo()",
        option2: "print()",
        option3: "printf()",
        option4: "output()",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is used to declare a variable in PHP?",
        option1: "$",
        option2: "@",
        option3: "#",
        option4: "&",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "Which PHP function is used to generate a random number?",
        option1: "rand()",
        option2: "random()",
        option3: "generateRandom()",
        option4: "randomNumber()",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "What is the correct way to end a PHP statement?",
        option1: ".",
        option2: ";",
        option3: ":",
        option4: ",",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is used to concatenate two strings in PHP?",
        option1: "+",
        option2: "&",
        option3: ".",
        option4: ",",
        ans: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "What is the result of the following code?\n```php\n$x = 10;\n$y = 5;\necho $x * $y;\n```",
        option1: "10",
        option2: "5",
        option3: "50",
        option4: "15",
        ans: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "What is the correct way to check if two values are equal in PHP?",
        option1: "=",
        option2: "==",
        option3: "===",
        option4: "!=",
        ans: 2,
    },
];
